Hello everyone, welcome back to this new tutorial session.
So today here I will create for the MySQL views, ok?
So first of all here, I can simply add the first segment for understanding the MySQL view.
So in this session for the MySQL view, our view is essentially in a virtual table that
is based on the result set of the MySQL statement.
It will be like a table and the query derived from the one or more underlining table.
So first of all simply here, create the first example like the slide for the query is
create a view based on the above is create table.
So now just extract and inside it, first you can start.
So here first of all create this for create the view.
So first of all here, going to our first underscore is called the view, ok?
And here I can add the statement and create the select for extract from the table is called
the customers, ok?
So define here perfectly and here simply just I can define here simply show the customer table
information of the data query, ok?
So now I can select and then execute and you can see here this comment is completely
successful and it will give MySQL provide the confirmation message, this one, ok?
So this then and I can completely use and now just here I can verify this content or review
using for here select for you, ok?
So now just bring another form and make sure it is open and here first of all I can just
type select then start from update name and here it is called the first underscore view,
ok?
So this one and here completely use and now just select all and then verify in this statement
or format so now you can just click on here and see this is the first view information
and the data for each table.
So first add the ID name address and then the salary column, ok?
So I hope you perfectly understand in this session, ok?
So the next step here create for another example and we can do not exist plus you can use
the replace plus along with the create will to replace the existing will.
So first of all here I can just go in in this state name so here first of all I can just
go in here and create for the replace or just your create for use the all states name and
then type here the replace view the first view as the select from the customer and it
is complete and here select and I am going to replace this and you can see here not replaced
yet is correct.
So in this situation, ok?
So here I can now different and go another way here I can create a view using the world
class for the table.
So now I can just use for in this or replace statement also create for the column and
define this is the clear view for use the test view, ok?
So the TESG view for else start from the customer and then type for here use the while
because for here the salary ok the salary is equal to the 3000 ok.
Now here simply different and first of all here I am going to select and execute and
you can see here this comment is completely successful ok.
And now here I am going to verify in this table information.
So now just here I can again select and execute and you can see here this is the all records
for 3000 for the record here between 2000, 15,000, 20,000, 25,000, 65,000 and 5,000 and 21,000
and we are completely down the greater than 3000 greater than all salary range ok.
So here is for another statement just here now and here can use for the clear view statement
along with the take option ok.
So you can see first of all here I can just use for here view.
So now just remove this statement and here I will just deploy first of all I am going
to create a new here I can create the new underscore the W and next step here I can going
to select statement use from the customer ok.
Then go to the next step and here use the where for support the name program is not
not ok and also here I can use for the read for take option ok.
So now here perfectly defined which is the take option and here I can select all and
execute now and here we have completely successfully added the statement and we can do another
new query and just verify this.
So first of all we have just created the select this term from the new underscore.
So here just use or create for the new you can just use.
So select and execute and you can see here it is completely changed for the table it is
perfect and here show all information ok.
So here in this session completely used for the MySQL view statement and I hope you
perfectly understand this session so thank you for watching and happy coding.